	//問題文を格納する要素です
	const quiz = [
        {
          question: "A large _____ of fish and sea mammals inhabit the coral reef off the western coast of the island.",
          answers: ["vary", "varying", "variety", "variation"],
          correct: "variety"
        },
        {
          question: "_____ wishing to be considered for the opening should submit an application to the personnel department.",
          answers: ["They", "Who", "That", "Those"],
          correct: "just"
        },
        {
          question: "Because of the Internet, information can be accessed _____ than at any time in the past.",
          answers: ["easier", "more easily" ,"easiest", "most easily"],
          correct: "more easily"
        },
        {
          question: "The internship offers an opportunity for gaining valuable experience _____ those wishing to enter the film industry.",
          answers: ["at", "of", "to", "by"],
          correct: "to"
        },
        {
          question: "Our company is commited to _____ natural resources via recycling programs and increased efficiency.",
          answers: ["conserving", "conserve", "conservation", "conserves"],
          correct: "conserving"
        },
        {
          question: "The president suggested that the company Web site be updated _____ two weeks.",
          answers: ["less", "every", "most", "much"],
          correct: "every"
        },
        {
          question: "We would prefer that the new office equipment _____ outside of our usual business hours.",
          answers: ["be installed", "to install", "has installed", "will install"],
          correct: "be installed"
        },
        {
          question: "_____ employees eat in the break room, they should make sure to properly dispose of any garbage.",
          answers: ["Always", "Following", "Nowadays", "Whenever"],
          correct: "Whenever"
        },
        {
          question: "There are too many candidates to speak with here today, so several interviews will be _____ at company headquarters next week.",
          answers: ["notified", "nominated", "conducted", "reminded"],
          correct: "conducted"
        },
        {
          question: "A sales _____ unexpectedly dropped by headquarters, asking to meet with the head of the purchasing department.",
          answers: ["represent", "representative", "representing", "representation"],
          correct: "representative"
        },
        {
          question: "_____ we expand internationally or continue operating only domestically depends on the results of the upcoming cross-border trade negotiations.",
          answers: ["Whichever", "Neither", "Whether", "Even"],
          correct: "Whether"
        },
        {
          question: "As he has saved a substantial amount of money, Mr.Leon will be establishing _____ company next month.",
          answers: ["on his", "he", "himself", "his own"],
          correct: "his own"
        },
        {
          question: "Although a sudden, heavy rainfall is helping firefighters control the blaze, it almost certainly will _____ the investigation into what caused the fire.",
          answers: ["wait", "delay", "remain", "occur"],
          correct: "delay"
        },
        {
          question: "The board asked Mr.Han to provide them with more detailed information and a _____ explanation of the proposal than he gave them in his original presentation.",
          answers: ["clear", "clearer", "clearly", "clearness"],
          correct: "clearer"
        },
        {
          question: "_____ of the packages show evidence of damage due to improper handling.",
          answers: ["Several", "Whichever", "Something", "Every"],
          correct: "Several"
        },
        {
          question: "A request _____ classified data files must be accompanied by a supervisor's written authorization.",
          answers: ["access", "to access", "access", "accsessible"],
          correct: "to access"
        },
        {
          question: "The first essay submitted by the student had numerous grammatical errors, _____ the second was nearly flawless.",
          answers: ["since", "while", "if", "after"],
          correct: "while"
        },
        {
          question: "The weather service predicts that it _____ more heavily than usual.",
          answers: ["has been raining", "is raining", "has rained", "will rain"],
          correct: "will rain"
        },
        {
          question: "A document _____ to this e-mail contains some important statistics obtained in the recent marketing study.",
          answers: ["combined", "assciated", "inserted", "attched"],
          correct: "attched"
        },
        {
          question: "Eagle Mart, one of the biggest shoe stores in town, stays _____ untill midnight on Fridays and Saturdays.",
          answers: ["open", "opening", "openly", "to open"],
          correct: "open"
        }
      ];
    
  